The next thing I'm going to talk to you about is chest lifts with accent.
We're going to add the accent to the chest lift that we just learned.
Again, it's very important to keep yourself in correct posture, tail bone tucked under, knees slightly bent, chest lifted.
You want to make sure your chin is level.
So for the chest lift, going back to the chest lift, lift and drop, lift and drop, lift and drop.
Again, right here from the rib cage, lift and drop, lift and drop.
Keeping the shoulders at a level pace here.
Lift and drop.
Now we're going to add the accents.
What you want to do is you want to put the accents on the ups so when you come up, up, real sharp, drop slow.
Up real sharp, and drop slow.
We can also put the accents on the bottom.
So what we're going to do is we're going to drop real heavy and lift.
Drop and lift, drop and lift, drop and lift, drop and lift.
Now from there you can pick up the pace.
We'll put the accent on the top.
So lift, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, and drop, one, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight.
That's your chest lift with accent.